Codes:
1. gif.ipynb
	used to test all the codes can run. 
	I used predict_mrcnn_gif.py in this notebook.

2. ImageAnalysis_mrcnn.py
	I used this to run repeatedly for all the days.
3. predict_mrcnn.py
	this is the function I used in ImageAnalysis_mrcnn.py, so make sure they are in the same folder.

Folders:
4. folder MaskRCNN_Train is where I used to train the mrcnn model. Code is YB_train_cow_TF2_8.ipynb, ran it in google colab with GPU.
5. folder mrcnn is the package folder, customized one by updating newest functions and models. 05-23-2023. This may change again when there are new versions again.
6. folder LabelMe is how to use labelme to manually label depth images.
